<Document>
  # NewHome sector welcome board

Welcome to the NewHome sector! This sector prioritizes the people residing inside it above all. Please make yourself comfortable.

[color=#33bbff]If you'd like a hand, ask on the radio, or talk to somebody.[/color]


## Local Economy and Sector Economy
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerBankATM"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SpaceCash1000"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerShipyard"/>
  </Box>
  Any money earned by you is [bold]yours[/bold] to keep, and will be available in future shifts if deposited at a [color=#44cc00]Sector ATM[/color] or [color=#44cc00]Local ATM[/color].
  You are likely to find an ATM at a local outpost, near some shops and banks.

To make money, why not:
- Join a ship's crew? Ask on the radio if anyone needs extra crew, and work to help your captain.
- Get a job on station or a planet? Message some [color=#009933]Local Outpost Representatives[/color] (messaging app in PDA([color=red]NOT IMPLEMENTED YET[/color])) if anything needs doing.
- Use a [color=#cccc00]shipyard console[/color] to purchase your own ship?

## Amenities
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineAstroVend"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineAmmo"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MachineCryoSleepPod"/>
  </Box>
  Some provisions (e.g. air tanks, salvage equipment) are available from vendors at any local Outpost, but most amenities (medical services, food) should be offered by other players on shuttles, player ran shops or at the Trade Depot.

Be sure to stock up at the Trade Depot if going out on an extended voyage, and take advantage of the [color=#33bbff]medical insurance tracker[/color] in your loadout, or from the NanoMed vendor in medbay.
  (Currently medical tracker is injected by default into everyone this will be changed)

NewHome rounds typically last for [color=#33bbff]one week[/color] before the server is reset for maintnence.
If you need to end your shift early or take a break, use the [color=#33bbff]cryo sleep chambers[/color] in the medbay on Frontier Outpost.
</Document>
